Nogizaka Chokkenchu
Huh? What?
Don!
Hi, nice to meet you, I'm Bananaman from Dogisakan Kouchushikai, nice to meet you.
I'm Gachan.
Oh, no, it's from here. - Oh, my goodness. - I'll be with you the whole time.
I'm with you all the way. - I'm with you all the way.
He's just adorable.
Today's project, Mr. Himura, please.
I'm with Yamashita.
That's right.
To send Yamashita off on a good note.
This time
Yamashita and I will play games together.
and try to clear all of them.
Starting from the 5th term, right?
You're starting with the 5th period?
Okay, then, Mr. Himura.
The fifth term will play with Yamashita...
Yamashita's famous scene quiz.
The 5th term students will be quizzed on Yamashita's famous scenes from the past 8 years of the show.
Three out of five questions must be answered correctly to clear the quiz.
What do you think, gentlemen?
How are you doing?
You'll feel so much better.
You'll be fine, won't you?
Yes.
What's up, Okuda?
Recently, when I had time...
I've been watching "famous scenes" of various people.
So you're strong.
Do you remember your best scenes, too?
I've been watching a lot of them.
Mas.
The place of the square.
Missing the location of the trout.
Hang in there, Kokisei, hang in there... are you confident? Nakanishi place... miss the place of the trout
Hang in there, Kokisei!
Are you confident, Nakanishi?
What can I say, I'm under a lot of pressure...
I don't remember making fun of you like this.
Have you been watching Nogizaka's show or something in the past?
I did.
I'm sure you watched Shokichi... because it was the 3rd term that made me fall in love with Nogizaka.
So you didn't really like the 12th term?
I'm glad... But still... Yamashita's famous scene quiz Question 1
Yamashita's first appearance with Sunshine Ikezawa
Golf swing
And what's the other one? I'm not saying it's a choice... I'm doing all of them.
I'm doing all of them.
Do you want to act it out a little?
Of course you remember, don't you, Yamashita?
Of course he remembers.
Sunshine Ikezaki used to do this a lot.
I had to rub it a lot.
May I have some? Sunshine?
No, no, no.
It's cocking time.
Can I have some Chinking Ikezaki?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'd be happy to.
Sunshine, the invincible idol of coincidental despair
YAMAMUSHIKAI
Here it is.
It's good.
The sharpness is totally good.
With a boost from Sunshine
What's your regulatory response?
Seino
Tea ceremony
Hmm?
Chado?
You mentioned tea ceremony.
I did the tea ceremony.
What was the correct answer?
I'll make the tea, please.
Thank you.
We don't know much either.
We do.
I'll pour hot water.
Keep your voice down.
I know it's too high, but it's a little embarrassing, embarrassing, embarrassing.
Oh, my God.
It's become so surreal.
It looks amazing!
It was delicious.
Thank you so much
So.
You're right!
Yay!
I'm so happy
That feels good.
I thought maybe I couldn't get it here.
I figured it out earlier.
For real?
Yoda's a little off.
Yoda's got it all picked out.
We got the second one.
Wow, that's really good.
It's really good.
Who did Yamashita do?
The 6-star's answer
It's interesting that people don't know the title.
Indeed it is
Seino
Mr. Yamashita
The correct answer is
Mukai Mukai, when you start walking from a sitting position, you can feel the evolution of mankind.
Yes, that's the correct answer.
Wow, Peach!
Yamashita, you really know your stuff.
That's amazing... even before I came in.
It's true... Ichinose remembered.
Mizuki's acting ability and Kazuki's surprisingly good.
I was surprised to find out that Mizuki is like this.
Wow, this is connected, isn't it, Drama A now?
The acting is very thrusting, isn't it?
By the way, the 4th season... you already knew this.
Kakki said he's already figured it out.
He's a Yamashita fan, right?
He's so strong.
Next up were Yamashita and Ito Lilia Livia, who rode the roller coaster of the Safe Express for her first reaction.
That's a cool question based on Yamashita's comment after this.
All right.
It's good.
Cute!
What's going on?
Yeah!
Ew.
It's going to Lilia's side.
First of all, it's not a game.
There's a serializer.
This is hard.
I'm not an oyster, but this is...
Yes, I was watching it, but I was enjoying it.
Of course.
That's right.
Yes, I was watching and enjoying it, so I'm wondering if I'll get the third question right and clear this game.
Well then...
Okay.
Thank you, Mom.
I like this one... the mouth is open so air can get inside.
It's like you're gently rocking like this.
I think you should remember that.
Ah.
Here we go.
Oh, no, that's great, that's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
Yay!
Awesome.
I thought I was saving your mom.
Well, you know, you were right.
That's great.
Feels good.
You're amazing, Mr. Yamakita!
I love high grades
I didn't think you'd remember so much
I'm so happy
Yamakita san, you made him happy!
Thank you, Yamakita, too, great job!
Thank you, Yamashita!
Thank you very much for your excellent fans!
I'm very happy to see such a good result, Yamashita!
It's a great feeling.
These kids are really good.
Can we have a game with 4th period and Yamashita?
Yamashita and I will try to answer each other's questions.
This is hard.
The 4th term students and Yamashita try to match the answers to the same question.
If you can match all the answers at least once out of three questions, you'll clear the game.
Yamashita, the 4th term students have known each other for a long time, haven't they?
Yes, we have been working together for about 6 years now.
We've been working together for about six years now, so I think we'll do well.
Especially in the summer.
Yes.
You know everything, don't you?
I know everything.
About Yamashita.
That's why I don't meet strange people.
Is there anyone who might say something weird?
The worst part is that Yumiki's here.
That's really bad.
You're underestimating him.
Of course it's underestimating.
Accommodating Mr. Yamashita is what I do best.
You're too used to it.
Backstage lunch box that raises the tension.
Please don't talk to me about it.
It's just that...
Can the 4th term students unite their hearts with Yamashita's and match their answers?
Let's start with the 4th term.
Ready, go!
Oh, my God, everything's not right here.
No one's got it right.
What? Does it say "pea"?
Kyuuken, what does it say "pea"? Kyouken.
Shumai.
If it's "kyoken", it's not the same anymore.
Kiouken, but...
Oh, Tsukada Farms.
We had lunch at Tsukada Farm today.
There it is!
I thought it might work.
So that's what they have!
That's for sure.
But at this point, I don't have a 4th period.
By the way, Yamashita's answer is
Yamashita.
That's two.
Tamura and Katsumi.
Yumiki is different.
Why are you saying Yumiki did it this way with Kanebei?
Please stop confusing me.
I'll react.
I wonder what he did.
The hardest thing to get punished for in Nogizaka Kenkouchu is...
All of them.
Oh, wait.
I think I'm going to win.
Yes, sir. Endo, any questions?
Yeah...
Why did you step out?
It's unusual for Endo...
I took a step out of anxiety.
Anxious... anxious steps.
Is that possible?
I'm going to go meet him.
No, everyone does that.
I'm going to go meet up with a limited number of people. Will Yamashita and the fourth term students be united next time?
Let's open the 4th term!
Ready?
Not anymore?
Too much whitewash?
What was Yamashita's answer?
I'm chattering.
I'm so scared.
You've been guessing all along.
I'm glad I missed it.
I'm a little happy.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, no.
This is the last one.
Final question.
I'm sure this one will be fine.
Which Nogizaka song do you think has the cutest choreography?
Cute!
There are almost 300 songs.
Nogizaka Mikke
I was too picky, so I limited my choices to 35 songs by my siblings.
If you want to match them, why don't you just put "An"?
You can show me, right?
What do you mean, "let me out"?
You want me to play Mr. Yamashita?
You shouldn't show too much.
What are you asking me about?
No, you can't.
Wait a little longer.
I think we should wait and change it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Okay, let's open the flip charts for the fourth quarter.
Oh, no, it's all falling apart.
I've been scolded by you... you scolded me... one man's paradise.
I didn't have it all together at this point.
I haven't seen Yamashita's yet.
I have a suggestion.
A suggestion.
I'd like to have one from each of the four seasons, to match Mr. Mizuki's.
That's right.
Yes, that's a good idea.
I see.
Okay, then.
This is going to be hard.
Let's not discuss it again, shall we?
You can change it one more time from the list.
The fourth term students may choose one of the answers.
What?
Who cares?
What kind?
Please stop it already... will the 4th term students' answers be aligned?
You scolded me.
You scolded me. That sums it up.
We didn't discuss this, did we?
Is this possible?
The baton reached Yamashita for the first time.
Are we as one now?
Please.
One person.
No.
May I?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought we cleared four terms.
I wonder what it would take to get it all.
I don't think we'll get it.
We'll have to work our way up to at least two choices. I really want the third term to be a success.
And a game with Yamashita in the third term, please.
A game in which you look back in the order of the other members to the music when you hear a theme.
This time, we will be divided into two groups, with Yamashita in each group.
If one of them succeeds, the game will be cleared.
Which one is Rin?
After about 10 times at the year-end party, we finally got him to do it!
First, the five of us tried it!
Will we succeed at the first try?
It's the last time we'll do it together.
We're in first place... well... in first place... and the last time we'll do it together.
It's the last time we'll do it on TV.
If we don't get it together, we're in trouble.
Then we'll have to line up.
That's right... Ume!
To make Yamashita graduate comfortably...
Let's give it one more shot.
Leave this to me.
Let's make it a rule not to be overconfident.
Be mindful of the image of those around you.
Yoda, are you okay?
I'll do it when I have to.
Really? I don't see much of him when he does it.
Today...
I don't know.
You'll have to decide today.
Let's go for it.
He's in. He's in.
We're in the same boat.
But this group...
They're pretty calm.
That's true.
It's all here.
All right, let's talk about a subject.
How are you? Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's go... in character, in character, in character, really.
I'm going to go.
Yes, please look forward.
I could have done it this way.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Clear!
What's this?
That's great!
Clear!
I know what I'm looking at!
Here we go!
It's so beautiful!
Oh, my gosh!
Cheer up.
It's hard.
Yamashita, are you the most Hatsunatsu type among all of them? Amazing! Cheerful and... difficult.
Yamashita is the most
He's the most energetic
Energetic
And who would you like as number 2?
Yes, I do.
Yoshida.
I don't know, I don't think Yoda.
Ume also seems to have an image of being calm and collected.
Zhuhai is not very energetic either.
Did you think Yamashita would go to the market?
I thought he might have an energetic image because of the excitement.
It's amazing from this area.
The third place I went to was also amazing.
I've read a lot.
You're energetic in your personal life, energetic at work.
When you turn it on...
That's what I'm talking about.
You're thinking that much in that one moment?
It's like we all read it that way.
That's why I cleared it.
But I'm going to give it another shot.
Will it be a consecutive success?
That's cute.
Here we go.
Chocolate Disco Game Start
Oh, wow...
That was close, that was close, that was close. - You're a character, you know that?
Gayloker.
I'm sorry, it's not a mockery.
Well, that's what you were trying to say.
But honestly, I've never seen you do that before.
I've never seen you do it, not even at first glance.
That's not the world I live in.
I made a mistake last time.
So... let's do a little self-analysis, shall we?
Like, "You're a cheapskate.
That's what I'm talking about.
Third term's cleared!
That feels good.
Let's go for a tearful one!
To the only two who didn't make it here, the fourth term students and Yamashita...
Let's really put the final answer together.
Let's send Yamashita off as one!
Let's unite and send Yamashita off!
Good luck!
Crying one time
Now the question
What's your first impression of Mr. Himura?
First impressions, so to speak.
That's what Mr. Yamashita would say.
Which way to go?
Let's all watch Mr. Himura together.
Ready, set, go!
What's this?
Are we doing first impressions again?
I think it's best to go with Yamashita.
Endo, you got a question?
I'm a little nervous. I'm sorry.
I'm the type of person who comes out of the office anxious.
It's better to go with a really flat line.
Let's keep it simple.
Keep it simple. I've already given you a super hint.
We want it to fit. We want it to fit, here.
I want to succeed in the fifth term, in the third term, in the fourth term only.
Thank you.
That's the first one from Nimura.
Yes, sir.
Now, can Yamashita and the fourth term students become one?
Really?
That's the first thing we have to do.
First impression of Mr. Nimura.
Open for the fourth term.
Dan.
Four-ball open three.
Yes, sir.
Wait a minute.
Hold on a second, please.
There's some people in there.
There's some people here.
Let me just go through them one by one.
Round.
Yes, Shibata.
Rave.
It can't be helped.
I didn't think so, I didn't think so.
And big
Simple
And large
Here it is.
Oh, no.
I don't think so.
I don't think... I don't think...
You don't think.
I don't think so.
Oysters are first impression pigs.
Oysters...
I really thought everyone would write "pig".
All of them.
That's why Yamashita says it feels so good.
You heard "pimp".
So now you have a chance to choose again from the answers.
Anyway, let's get Yamashita.
Let's go!
Let's do it in unison!
Here we go... pig, pig, pig, pig, pig!
Even Endo wrote "pig.
I don't think so.
There are many ways to say "pig".
katakana while opening kanji
All of them have "pig" in them.
You don't think so.
I'm just trying to fit it in.
The writing has been a pig from the beginning
I wonder if it's connected to Yamashita, the fourth generation student who has awakened to the variety.
Will Yamashita fit in?
Come on, pig!
It can't be helped now, come as a pig!
Open
Big!
Pigs
pig
Pig on top of pig. Pig! Pig! Pig!
Pig!
Did I write that from the beginning?
I did, pig.
You think it's a pig?
What do you call a big fat one?
A pig!
Pig!
Well, then, you've done it!
That's not funny, that's not funny.
This is not funny.
I was one of the members of the younger generation that was leading the group so strongly.
Yamashita Oh, I was surprised that he was graduating.
You know, when I watched the old VTR and Yamashita's VTR, he's so young.
Your face is so young.
He looks so young now that he's a celebrity.
I think she has become a celebrity.
Idol and actress.
I think you've really made your mark.
Looking back on the show, what were some of your most memorable moments?
Well, the Valentine's Day project was pretty memorable.
I'm not a very talkative person myself.
I'm not a very talkative person, and I tend to be reserved with my juniors.
But it was a place where I could reaffirm myself.
A place where I can reflect on myself
I need to talk more.
I'm a shy person.
I'm a shy person, so this is the place where I could get to know my juniors better.
Since the Valentine's Day event, I've been going out to eat with my juniors
I started to keep in touch with them.
Yamashita and Asuka were very aggressive with me.
Congratulations!
He took the initiative to get into some interesting relationships with her.
I totally understand.
Even when it's a little embarrassing...
She does her best.
It's not often that a beautiful woman becomes funny.
I feel like I'm a part of the show every week.
Even though I'm on the show every week.
I get nervous every time, even though I've been doing it for eight years.
I wonder if I'll be able to speak today, or what I'll do if I'm suddenly asked to do something.
Yamashita-san, you're a veteran who's now the type of person who leads the way, so you were nervous?
I was really nervous. I'm not the type of person who is good at variety shows, so I was nervous, but once the show started, I always had a lot of fun, and I really grew and got to know the members better.
I would like to thank the fans who watched the show.
To the fans who watched this show, thank you very much.
I would like to thank the 3rd, 4th, 5th, and maybe even 6th term students who have watched this show.
And 6th term students will probably join us from now on.
Please continue to support Nogizaka46 and this show as it continues to grow and develop.
Thank you very much.
Well then, congratulations on your graduation.
That's beautiful.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much and keep up the good work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for your hard work.
Tickets for Mizuki Yamashita's graduation concert are now on sale!
Hello everyone!
This is Mizuki Yamashita.
I've just finished recording the last episode of "Nogizaka Chiken Chu" and I'm so sad and lonely.
I'm so sad and lonely.
I'm so sad... I'm so sad... I'm so sad... I'm so sad...
I'm sure everyone will continue to make it a fun show every time.
I'm sure everyone will continue to make this show fun and exciting.
Please watch it every week no matter what!
I'll miss you so much.
Please!
So, please subscribe to our channel.
Please subscribe to our channel.